celebritybrideguide.com 2011-09-16

# Privacy Policy - Celebrity Bride Guide

## Privacy Policy

Last Updated: May 22, 2009

 **1\. INTRODUCTION**

 **1.1. Purpose of Policy**  
Welcome to CelebrityBrideGuide.com. Tail Light Media, Inc. (“us,” “we,” or “Tail Light”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the CelebrityBrideGuide.com web site (the “Web Site”). We created this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Web Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Web Site, and not to any other web sites that you may be able to access from the Web Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

 **1.2. Notice Concerning Children**  
We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children 13 years of age or under. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Web Site user is age 13 or under, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

 **2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

 **2.1. What Basic Information Do We Collect?**  
In operating the Web Site, Tail Light may include registration, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, date of birth, and other contact information, credit card information for purchases, as well as other user profile information, including without limitation, gender, education, occupation and images and videos you submit.

 **2.2. What Additional Information Do We Collect?**

(a) _Automatic Collection_. Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Web Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

(b) _Cookies_. From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Web Site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our Web Site other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Web Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

 **3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION**

 **3.1. What Does Tail Light Do With Collected Information?**

(a) _Personal Information_. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Web Site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the Web Site, to send you additional information about Tail Light, or to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you give your permission during the account registration process, we may share your contact information with our business partners or other companies so that they may send you promotional materials. If you choose to post a comment on the Web Site, your name (as you enter it) will be displayed to all users of the Web Site to facilitate interaction among users. Users email addresses are never revealed to other users.

(b) _Anonymous Information_. We use anonymous information to analyze our Web Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

(c) _Use of Cookies_. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

(d) _Disclosure of Personal Information_. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Tail Light or its affiliates, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Tail Light or the users of the Web Site, or (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Web Site.

(e) _Sale of Assets_. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through the Web Site. If Tail Light or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

(f) _Access to Information / Opting-Out_. If you have opted to subscribe to our email newsletter, you may unsubscribe at any time by using the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email newsletter.  
**  
4\. SECURITY**  
The Web Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

 **5\. SITE AREAS BEYOND TAIL LIGHT’S CONTROL**

 **5.1. Public Forums**  
The Web Site includes interactive forums for the exchange of information, ideas and opinions. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information.

 **5.2. Third Party Web Sites**  
The Web Site may contain links to other web sites. If you choose to visit other web sites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other web sites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those web sites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

 **6\. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES**

 **6.1. Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to the Web Site, please contact us at the following e-mail address: privacy@celebritybrideguide.com.

 **6.2. Updates and Changes**  
We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Web Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
